It's not like they didn't warn us.
Signs is a drama, thriller, science fiction film directed by M. Night Shyamalan.
A family living on a farm finds mysterious crop circles in their
fields which suggests something more frightening to come.
Graham Hess, played by Mel Gibson.
Merrill Hess, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Morgan Hess, played by Rory Culkin.
Bo Hess, played by Abigail Breslin.
Officer Paski, played by Cherry Jones.
Ray Reddy, played by M. Night Shyamalan.
Signs is a 2002 American science fiction horror
thriller film written and directed by M.
Night Shyamalan and produced by Shyamalan, Frank
Marshall, Kathleen Kennedy and Sam Mercer.
The film was produced by Touchstone Pictures, Blinding Edge
Pictures and The Kennedy/Marshall Company.
It was distributed by Buena Vista Pictures.
Starring Mel Gibson and Joaquin Phoenix, the story focuses on a former Episcopal priest named Graham Hess who discovers
a series of crop circles in his cornfield and that the phenomenon is a result of extraterrestrial life.
Signs explores the themes of faith, kinship, and extraterrestrials.
Signs premiered in theaters on August 2, 2002.
The film was a financial success, grossing $408 million on a $72 million budget, becoming the seventh-highest-grossing film of 2002, and was met with positive
reviews from critics, with many praising its atmosphere, performances, cinematography, score and story, but others criticizing aspects of the script.
The film was nominated for multiple awards, including those from the
Online Film Critics Society and the Empire Awards.
The film also won an award from the American Society
of Composers, Authors and Publishers.
The high definition Blu-ray Disc edition of the film featuring the director's audio commentary, the
making of the film and deleted scenes was released in the United States on June 3, 2008.
The original motion picture soundtrack, which was composed by James Newton Howard,
was released on the opening day by the Hollywood Records label.
The film explores themes of farm, faith,
symbolism, miracle, family relationships.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and thought_provoking.